Zhijiang Infinite Capacity Technology (Zhejiang) Co., Ltd. Zhejiang Yanhe Culture Technology Co., Ltd.
Your Highness should check
Chu Xiaoxiao's files.
I believe you'll find something.
Princess,
you actually know these details so well.
I thought...
What did you think?
That I was a woman who only cared about the manor
and ignored the affairs of the world?
It is so hard to be the Princess of Ling.
Being too smart invites suspicion.
Talking too much brings trouble.
Actually,
I also know how to investigate cases.
Why don't we investigate
together from tomorrow?
That way, we can also...
I'm a bit tired.
I want to get some rest.
Will Your Highness
still sleep in the study tonight?
Yes.
I still have some things to figure out.
It seems that
Your Highness prefers the role of Shen Zhao.
But don't forget,
you are the master of this manor after all.
Leave the investigations
to the government office.
Rest early.
Come in.
What's the situation?
Why are you rich kids up so early today?
I found out.
Found out what?
The real killer
is A Xiao.
Her real name is Chu Xiaoxiao.
She is Chu Feng's sister.
How did you find out?
Who do you think I am?
I found it through this fabric.
A Xiao.
Isn't she Musician Han's maid?
She's not.
She's a musician from Chang'an.
A musician?
Lord Su!
Bad news!
Li Qingluan is going to Zuixian Restaurant
to have a musical duel with Ashina Xiao.
He even put up a notice
saying he'll avenge his master and Senior Brother Cui.
Oh no.
Let's go.
Hurry.
Will someone die again this time?
I see Li Qingluan is very confident.
He will definitely beat Ashina Xiao.
Western Regions brat!
Today,
I will make you die.
Brother Chu Feng, after today's tune,
your revenge will be complete.
You can rest in peace.
Cut the crap.
Today,
with the real 'Nanshan Youtai' in hand,
I will definitely beat you.
Second Senior Brother.
This is the real 'Nanshan Youtai' music score
left by the master.
I don't know where First Senior Brother got his,
but it must be fake.
First Senior Brother is always arrogant,
and Third Senior Brother is weak and incompetent.
In my heart,
only the righteous Second Senior Brother
is qualified to inherit the master's 'Nanshan Youtai'.
Senior Brother Qingluan.
This is the 'Nanshan Youtai'
the master kept secret his whole life.
It was originally meant for Senior Brother Chu Feng.
But Senior Brother Chu Feng is gone,
and the master favors Senior Brother Cui.
He never cared about you at all.
With this score,
you can definitely beat Ashina Xiao.
Let everyone know
that you are the best musician in Fangzhou.
Right.
Master was blind.
Even a good-for-nothing like Cui Yujing could be First Senior Brother.
He deserved to die.
Actually, I am Master's best student.
Yes.
I've always thought so.
In my heart,
you are the best.
A Xiao.
As long as you beat Ashina Xiao,
I will
be with you.
Then we will leave Fangzhou together,
open your own music academy,
and never have to look at others' faces again.
A Xiao.
You understand me the best.
Make way.
We are still a step too late.
Stop.
Don't play anymore.
What's going on?
Because I put Gu poison in your well water.
How are you so powerful?
Who exactly are you?
Young Master Shen's melody disturbed Ashina Xiao.
He has gone mad.
Ashina Xiao.
You conspired with A'xiao
to kill people with Gu poison and fake music scores.
Confess your crimes!
Why are you framing me?
Chu Xiaoxiao.
Stop pretending.
Your brother is Chu Feng.
You are a musician from Chang'an.
This piece of cloth is from your clothes.
This time,
you are here to avenge your brother.
A'xiao.
Lord Su.
You are truly a great detective.
It really is you.
Catch the zither!
Today,
I will avenge my brother.
All of you onlookers are guilty.
Once I play the final chapter of the 'Insect Gu Ballad',
you will all be buried with my brother.
A'xiao, stop!
Brother Chu Feng wouldn't want you
to kill innocent people.
Don't shoot!
Let's go!
Chase them!
Come on!
Brother,
you have been avenged.
You can rest in peace now.
That skull belongs to Chu Feng.
Chu Xiaoxiao.
You killed innocent people for revenge.
Aren't you afraid of divine punishment?
Kill innocent people?
Who is exactly killing innocent people?